Daniel Keenan

Personal Statement

I am due to graduate from Kingston University with a Data Science MSc, which included extensive computing and data-focused experience. I am also a graduate of a Computer Science BSc, during which I completed a wide range of varied computing projects and further developed my existing skillset. I am now keen to utilise the skills I have gained from both degrees and gain work experience in an analyst role that provides challenge.

Key Skills & Experience

Technical Skills:

- Programming: Python, SQL, R, Java, JavaScript, Swift, HTML
- Data Analysis and Machine Learning: Pandas, NumPy, Matplotlib, Scikit-learn, Tensorflow, Keras, Tidyverse
- Software: MS Office Suite, Tableau, Power BI, VS Code, PyCharm, Anaconda, Jupyter Notebooks, MySQL/PostgreSQL, Git

Essential Skills:

- Sharp attention to detail and a strong analytical mindset
- Confident communicator
- Customer service and complaints handling
- Team player
- Willingness to learn new tools and practices

Education and Qualifications

September 2020 - September 2021: Kingston University

MSc in Data Science: Distinction

September 2015 - July 2019: Kingston University (Inc foundation year)

BSc Hons in Computer Science: First Class

September 2012 - August 2014: Luton Sixth Form College 3 A-Levels: Psychology: C, Computing: D, Mathematics: E

September 2007 - July 2012: Stopsley High School

10 GCSEs: A*- C including Maths and English

Address: 73 Lingfield Avenue, Kingston-upon-Thames, KT1 2TL Mobile: 07701387868

Email: dejk@hotmail.co.uk

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/daniel-keenan-1b7abb18a/ Portfolio Projects: https://danielkeenan.github.io/DKPortfolio/

Work Experience

Retail Assistant

Primark Stores LTD – July 2020 to Present

- Rotating, ordering, and maintaining stock
- Using POS system to complete customer transactions
- Responsible for overseeing designated areas of a shop floor
- Working as a team to ensure standards are consistently met
- First point of contact for gueries and complaints

Associate Application Specialist Signant Health – March 2020 to June 2020

- Designing and implementing custom data processing applications
- Complying with standards of practice and ensuring high-quality work
- Troubleshooting documents and performing code reviews to identify and resolve bugs and faults
- Assisting other members of technical services to support the team and maintain the quality of work throughout all projects using software including but not limited to JIRA, Excel, and Teams.

Retail Assistant

Primark Stores LTD – August 2017 to February 2020

As above

Events Assistant

Kingston University - October 2016 to July 2017

- Performing data-related admin tasks using Excel to ensure events and clients are properly documented
- Coordinating multiple events on various campuses with conflicting deadlines
- Diarising to ensure appropriate venues and facilities were allocated
- Overseeing the execution of events to ensure they are delivered according to plan
- Escorting panel guests and attending to any queries or needs

Telephone Interviewer GFK NOP – March 2013 to September 2015

- Performing market research by contacting members of the public
- Collecting and recording data and information
- Achieving personal targets to contribute towards a shared team goal

References available upon request.

Address: 73 Lingfield Avenue, Kingston-upon-Thames, KT1 2TL Mobile: 07701387868

Email: dejk@hotmail.co.uk

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/daniel-keenan-1b7abb18a/ Portfolio Projects: https://danielkeenan.github.io/DKPortfolio/